[
  {"number":1,"question":"The satellite photographed a moon previously undetected in orbit around Saturn.","answer":"previously undetected"},
  {"number":2,"question":"We were completely unaware of the problems with the air-conditioning units in the hotel rooms until this week.","answer":"completely"},
  {"number":3,"question":"Mr. Kemper's donation to the KSC community Foundation broke the record for the largest private gift ever given to the organization.","answer":"ever"},
  {"number":4,"question":"\"Accounts receivable\" is money owed to a company, whereas \"accounts payable\" is money owed by the company to creditors.","answer":"whereas"},
  {"number":5,"question":"The lectures will cover the relevant methods of determining the impact of currency fluctuations on international transactions.","answer":"determining"},
  {"number":6,"question":"The comptroller has predicted that in ten years the space used by research department will have to double.","answer":"predicted"},
  {"number":7,"question":"Many workers can't use computers; consequently training is required.","answer":"consequently"},
  {"number":8,"question":"In Piazzo's latest architectural project, he hopes to demonstrate his flare for blending contemporary and traditional ideas.","answer":"demonstrate"},
  {"number":9,"question":"Cooks must remember that some raw food are very perishable and should be refrigerated or chilled until ready to be eaten or cooked.","answer":"perishable"},
  {"number":10,"question":"Could you have the assistant stop by my office before he leaves today?","answer":"stop by"},
  {"number":11,"question":"Automobiles are put out of gear by moving the gear shift to neutral.","answer":"out"},
  {"number":12,"question":"Let's not tell the media too much about the deal.","answer":"Let's not"},
  {"number":13,"question":"Before adopting a particular distribution strategy, a segment of the market should be tested.","answer":"adopting"},
  {"number":14,"question":"Unfortunately, there are those who will probably not respect the arbiter's decision.","answer":"those who"},
  {"number":15,"question":"I am surprised they moved your office next to mine.","answer":"mine"},
  {"number":16,"question":"Practically no one in the group passed up the opportunity to attend computer skills seminar.","answer":"no one"},
  {"number":17,"question":"The members would resign if they were asked to do so.","answer":"were"},
  {"number":18,"question":"There was hardly any food left when we arrived at the party.","answer":"any"},
  {"number":19,"question":"Unfortunately, neither Mr. Sachs nor Mrs. Flynn will be able to attend the awards banquet this evening.","answer":"nor"},
  {"number":20,"question":"It's important that the clients seem interested.","answer":"seem"},
  {"number":21,"question":"Dance is the subject of several movies playing over the holiday season.","answer":"several"},
  {"number":22,"question":"What have you decided to do about the Skeyes case three days ago?","answer":"have you decided to do"},
  {"number":23,"question":"The trend toward shorter working hours continues.","answer":"continues"},
  {"number":24,"question":"Economic experts believe there will be a gradual slowdown in October.","answer":"slowdown"},
  {"number":25,"question":"Ms Nyguen had submitted her resume before she knew the position was filled.","answer":"knew"},
  {"number":26,"question":"The paychecks will be delivered when they arrive from the accounting department.","answer":"when"},
  {"number":27,"question":"The ceiling fans were on, but unfortunately they only stirred up the hot, humid air.","answer":"stirred up"},
  {"number":28,"question":"The country hospital is currently looking for volunteers to staff the reception.","answer":"looking for"},
  {"number":29,"question":"Have a heavy workload this month.","answer":"have"},
  {"number":30,"question":"Many employees seem more confused now about how to use the new telephone system than they did before they attended the workshop.","answer":"confused"},
  {"number":31,"question":"The administration allows Thailand and Indonesia trade benefits.","answer":"and"},
  {"number":32,"question":"A storm is coming and our radio doesn't work. Don't forget to buy another.","answer":"to buy another"},
  {"number":33,"question":"The dispute was settled on Saturday.","answer":"dispute"},
  {"number":34,"question":"He drinks too much, doesn't he?","answer":"doesn't he"},
  {"number":35,"question":"From the turn of the century, concern for wildlife has led to numerous international conservation programs.","answer":"has led"},
  {"number":36,"question":"My car broke down and I had to walk five miles to the nearest garage.","answer":"broke down"},
  {"number":37,"question":"When corporations decide to buy life insurance for their executives, the various plans should be evaluated like any other financial commitment.","answer":"evaluated"},
  {"number":38,"question":"I generally used to value my wife's opinion about my previous jobs.","answer":"value"},
  {"number":39,"question":"A consulting firm will help us find software.","answer":"consulting"},
  {"number":40,"question":"If the bills aren't paid in five days, the company will seek damages.","answer":"aren't paid"},
  {"number":41,"question":"As the filming location has not yet been determined, the release date has been postponed.","answer":"determined"},
  {"number":42,"question":"Tom strongly recommends that the sales people be more proactive.","answer":"be"},
  {"number":43,"question":"The business lunch organizers will call us as soon as they have time.","answer":"have"},
  {"number":44,"question":"Proposed changes that are not compliant with existing safety regulations will not be considered.","answer":"compliant"},
  {"number":45,"question":"Nick is a top salesman in our office, isn't he?","answer":"isn't he"},
  {"number":46,"question":"Mr. Pollock had reported for work when the weather conditions suddenly worsened.","answer":"had reported"},
  {"number":47,"question":"The work orders have been released to the production department.","answer":"released"},
  {"number":48,"question":"This presentation will demonstrate how Metron computers are superior to those of our competitors in terms of both features and speed.","answer":"to"},
  {"number":49,"question":"The talks will take place in Brussels.","answer":"in"},
  {"number":50,"question":"Executives of small companies earn higher salaries on the west coast than on the east coast.","answer":"higher"},
  {"number":51,"question":"If I had not seen it, I wouldn't have believed it possible.","answer":"had not"},
  {"number":52,"question":"For the museum visitor as well as for the veteran museum goer, the Museum Highlights Tour offers an excellent opportunity to see the most popular exhibits.","answer":"as well as"},
  {"number":53,"question":"Consumer confidence fell in April.","answer":"in"},
  {"number":54,"question":"Before anyone could even think about it, our accountant had predicted that their company would go bankrupt.","answer":"had predicted"},
  {"number":55,"question":"Count on Mr Jeffries to get the job done.","answer":"count on"},
  {"number":56,"question":"The human heart is wider at the top than at the bottom.","answer":"than"},
  {"number":57,"question":"The corporate headquarters are located in the capital of the country.","answer":"of"},
  {"number":58,"question":"A trade union would not accept the layoffs of the employees demanding.","answer":"demanding"},
  {"number":59,"question":"To vacation at the mountain resort, you must make reservations two to three months beforehand.","answer":"beforehand"},
  {"number":60,"question":"There are over thirty keyboard commands that can prompt word-processing procedures, but common usage involves only a few.","answer":"involves"},
  {"number":61,"question":"The telecommunications department is completing a detailed evaluation of each factory site to determine the types of equipment and features needed in each area.","answer":"evaluation"},
  {"number":62,"question":"I'm fed up with catching a bus all the time.","answer":"fed up"},
  {"number":63,"question":"The company offers a retirement plan for its workers.","answer":"retirement"},
  {"number":64,"question":"You need about forty different nutrients to stay healthy.","answer":"healthy"},
  {"number":65,"question":"The report outlines the products for the quarter of the year.","answer":"of"},
  {"number":66,"question":"James has been sick for a while; he seems unable to take care of himself.","answer":"take care of"},
  {"number":67,"question":"She took care of her old grandmother.","answer":"took care of"},
  {"number":68,"question":"After Mr Hague finished the job interview, he felt relieved.","answer":"after"},
  {"number":69,"question":"The prime is expected to arrive at the convention hall at approximately 7:00 P.M.","answer":"approximately"},
  {"number":70,"question":"On average employees reach their peak performance level when they have been in the job for at least two years.","answer":"average"},
  {"number":71,"question":"The performance of Michael is better than any other member in the team.","answer":"any other"},
  {"number":72,"question":"Armstrong has the most impressive management team of the three companies under consideration.","answer":"most impressive"},
  {"number":73,"question":"The notebook computer is the most profitable of all the products that are presently on sale.","answer":"most"},
  {"number":74,"question":"Mr Dalla would like the invoices faxed directly to Milan.","answer":"faxed"},
  {"number":75,"question":"Tina spent a long time looking for the right way to go.","answer":"looking"},
  {"number":76,"question":"Because our productivity figures improve in the near future, we foresee having to hire more people between now and July.","answer":"because"},
  {"number":77,"question":"If our candidates are elected, we'll have a strong board.","answer":"are"},
  {"number":78,"question":"After four years in domestic sales, Mr Leconte finally was able to transfer to the international division.","answer":"finally"},
  {"number":79,"question":"Ms. Lopez has already learned to created zip files.","answer":"already"},
  {"number":80,"question":"Some employees get their paychecks automatically deposited in their bank accounts.","answer":"deposited"},
  {"number":81,"question":"If I were in San Francisco, I would have visited the Golden Gate bridge.","answer":"were"},
  {"number":82,"question":"Mr Kekkonen accused Boris of procrastinating when he handed in this report a week late.","answer":"procrastinating"},
  {"number":83,"question":"The bank invites you to keep your securities safe in our vault under strict audit controls.","answer":"under"},
  {"number":84,"question":"What a shame! If Mrs. Dwayne hadn't been so disorganized, she would be given far more responsibilities.","answer":"hadn't been"},
  {"number":85,"question":"Make sure to use an authorized dealer.","answer":"authorized"},
  {"number":86,"question":"Extreme caution should be used when the forklift truck is being operated.","answer":"caution"},
  {"number":87,"question":"Since when have you been negotiating with Japanese potential customers?","answer":"have you been negotiating"},
  {"number":88,"question":"It is worth examining the steps nations can take to facilitate the removal barriers.","answer":"steps"},
  {"number":89,"question":"If savings could have been made elsewhere, we would have continued to give financial support to local community service organizations last year.","answer":"would have continued"},
  {"number":90,"question":"Find out the details and write a report.","answer":"out"},
  {"number":91,"question":"In this company there has been little regard for the needs of part-time workers.","answer":"regard"},
  {"number":92,"question":"Battery-operated reading lamps are selling very well right now.","answer":"are selling"},
  {"number":93,"question":"We are a major international company with a growing number of interests in North America.","answer":"interests"},
  {"number":94,"question":"Quarterly earnings are seldom reported to the shareholders.","answer":"seldom"},
  {"number":95,"question":"Management let the employees leave at two o'clock.","answer":"leave"},
  {"number":96,"question":"Participation in the saving plan is voluntary, but often reaches ninety percent.","answer":"voluntary"},
  {"number":97,"question":"Price quotes have been daily announced.","answer":"have been daily announced"},
  {"number":98,"question":"We conduct our audits in accordance with generally accepted auditing standards.","answer":"with"},
  {"number":99,"question":"The manager of the accounting department is flying to France next week.","answer":"is flying"},
  {"number":100,"question":"Faculty members are planning to hold a party in honor of Dr. Walker, who will retire at the end of the semester.","answer":"hold"},
  {"number":101,"question":"Would you please buy me some beer when you go to the SOG market?","answer":"some"},
  {"number":102,"question":"In order to place a call outside the office, you have to dial nine first.","answer":"dial"},
  {"number":103,"question":"I was so busy today that I hardly had time to eat at all.","answer":"hardly had"},
  {"number":104,"question":"Though their performance was relatively unpolished, the actors had the audience's attention for the duration of the play.","answer":"attention"},
  {"number":105,"question":"Today many managers reward only good performers and tend to dismiss incompetent employees more frequently.","answer":"incompetent"},
  {"number":106,"question":"I'm not going to stay here any longer. I won't come here any more.","answer":"any more"},
  {"number":107,"question":"After the main course, choose from our wide variety of homemade desserts.","answer":"variety"},
  {"number":108,"question":"This identification card is valid as long as your policy remains in effect.","answer":"effect"},
  {"number":109,"question":"When you cross the street, you must take care of speedy cars.","answer":"take care of"},
  {"number":110,"question":"I'm afraid Ms. Quattrano would not have been hired if she had not applied earlier this month.","answer":"would not have been hired"},
  {"number":111,"question":"If you send in an order by mail, we recommend that you phone our sales division directly to confirm the order.","answer":"by"},
  {"number":112,"question":"Private financing can take a variety of forms.","answer":"take"},
  {"number":113,"question":"If they do not like it, they can have another one.","answer":"do not"},
  {"number":114,"question":"Although we had left home on time, we arrived at the airport much later than we expected.","answer":"later"},
  {"number":115,"question":"Improvements in the local bus service have brought increased business to the area.","answer":"improvements"},
  {"number":116,"question":"This company attempts to make its employees feel like family.","answer":"feel"},
  {"number":117,"question":"We are pleased to inform you that the missing order has been found.","answer":"you"},
  {"number":118,"question":"Rates for the use of recreational facilities do not include tax and are subject to change without notice.","answer":"notice"},
  {"number":119,"question":"Responses to the proposed work schedule changes are still outstanding from several departments.","answer":"still"},
  {"number":120,"question":"If it had not rained yesterday, Mary might have come.","answer":"had not"},
  {"number":121,"question":"Naturally the company will try to borrow money at a low rate of interest, but loans of this kind are not frequently obtainable.","answer":"frequently"},
  {"number":122,"question":"A recent global survey suggests both demand for aluminum and tin will remain at its current level for the next five to ten years.","answer":"both"},
  {"number":123,"question":"The survey shows that the product will be popular in the market, unless the company cuts down the selling price of 10%.","answer":"unless"},
  {"number":124,"question":"The director of Educational Programs works collaboratively with the Ministry of Education to ensure that the programs are meeting the needs of the institution.","answer":"ensure"},
  {"number":125,"question":"Therefore costs should be cut, the number of staff positions will be reduced.","answer":"therefore"},
  {"number":126,"question":"You can't rent any vehicle unless you have a license.","answer":"unless"},
  {"number":127,"question":"We'll go on with the work, whether we can find the essential tools or not.","answer":"whether"},
  {"number":128,"question":"The meeting has been going on since eight o'clock this morning.","answer":"has been"},
  {"number":129,"question":"If the National Park had not been constructed 30 years ago, the citizens might still be looking for recreation among the rocks.","answer":"had not been"},
  {"number":130,"question":"The recent storms have led to the temporary closure of our overseas office.","answer":"temporary"},
  {"number":131,"question":"Savant National Park is accessible by train, bus, charter plane, and rental car.","answer":"accessible"},
  {"number":132,"question":"The young intern who was hired last month is quite knowledgeable about accounting.","answer":"knowledgeable"},
  {"number":133,"question":"The consultant could have doubled his business if had advertised.","answer":"could have doubled"},
  {"number":134,"question":"I haven't heard from my aunt since she left Taiwan.","answer":"heard from"},
  {"number":135,"question":"Jenna is unemployed, so she doesn't currently work.","answer":"doesn't currently work"},
  {"number":136,"question":"Inflation is likely to affect personal spending quite a bit in July.","answer":"likely"},
  {"number":137,"question":"The new office is almost three times the size of the old one.","answer":"three times the size of"},
  {"number":138,"question":"The chairman suggests targeting new international markets.","answer":"targeting"},
  {"number":139,"question":"It is one of the most interesting books on the topic.","answer":"most interesting"},
  {"number":140,"question":"The printer apologized for leaving out two names on the program.","answer":"leaving out"},
  {"number":141,"question":"Mrs Barker gave a short speech after lunch to express her appreciation for the retirement gift.","answer":"appreciation"},
  {"number":142,"question":"Coral, popular for necklaces, is made of tiny sea animals.","answer":"is"},
  {"number":143,"question":"The bank will be opening another branch in Houston within the next year.","answer":"will be opening"},
  {"number":144,"question":"The purchaser wanted the equipment delivered by Monday morning.","answer":"delivered"},
  {"number":145,"question":"If Mr Darwin were looking for a permanent job, our recruiter could help.","answer":"could"}
]
